# Jeremy Moseley

jeremy@jeremymoseley.net 1-415-926-1955

\*\*Jeremy is a focussed developer who is intrigued by the design and architecture of distributed systems. He has experience with distributed systems in Java, Scala, and Python, and has dabbled in everything from Javascript and HTML to databases and operating systems.

GitHub imoseley LinkedIn Jeremy Moseley

#### **SKILLS**

DISTRIBUTED SYSTEMS	Queues, Shared Memory, Databasees, Redis, SQS, RabbitMQ, Memcache, Sharding, Distributed System Design
DATABASE	MySQL, PostgreSQL, ORM, Slick
CLOUD	AWS, EC2, S3, Route53
WEB DEVELOPMENT	JavaScript, HTML 5, CSS, LAMP, REST, PHP, Postgresql

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Inkling Systems Inc.

Software Engineer 3 Jun 2015 - Present

Maintain and develop a legacy system for transforming markup, as well as develop a new service for importing various types of content.

- Architected and deployed a new system for importing content.
- Mentored several interns.

# **Inkling Systems Inc.**

Infrstructure Engineer Jun 2014 - Jun 2015

One member of a three man team to manage the AWS system that powers the entire service. Also worked to develop internal tools to help other teams own their own infrastucture. Migrated the distributed logging system from Facebook Scribe to a Fluentd, Elasticsearch, and Kibana based system to provide better insight into the workings of the system, and allow easier and faster diagnosis of problems in the system.

- Redesigned the entire distributed logging system.
- Operated as a member of the emergency on-call rotation.

# Inkling Systems Inc.

Platform Engineering Intern Sep 2013 - Dec 2013

Worked on the deployment of an XML database for allowing fast searches of marked up content, as well as the development of features on the core API.

■ Helped write complex XQuery scripts and API.

### **Internet Shakespeare Editions**

Part-time Developer Oct 2012 - Aug 2013

Worked as a part-time member of a team while in school, using XQuery and XPath to maintain and develop new features for a long-term academic project run by the English department. Deisnged a mobile experience for an originally desktop browser only website, as well as used XQuery and XPath to process and transform marked up content in a variety of interesting ways, depending on how the content was being consumed.

#### Vineyard Networks

Co-op Engineer Jan 2012 - Aug 2012

Developed deep packet inspection (DPI) plugins for a software package that runs on network hardware.

 Learned to analyze raw network traffic to extract patterns for various traffic types (HTTP, TCP, UDP, etc)

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **University of Victoria**

Sep 2009 - May 2014

GPA: 6.39

# **SAIT Polytechnic**

Jan 2006 - Dec 2007

GPA: 4.0

# **LANGUAGES**

**English** 

#### **INTERESTS**

mountain biking

#### technology

- technology
- research
- user experience

• future